# Bum-bum-bum-bum Bum-bum-bum-bum Bum-bum-bum-bum-bum #
- Mister Sandman , bring me a dream # - Bum-bum-bum-bum #
- # Make him the cutest That I 've ever seen # - # Bum-bum-bum-bum #
- # Give him two lips Like roses and clover # - # Bum-bum-bum-bum #
# Then tell him that his lonesome nights are over #
- # Sandman , I 'm so alone # - # Bum-bum-bum-bum #
- # Don 't have nobody to call my own # - # Bum-bum-bum-bum #
# Please turn on your magic beam #
# Mister Sandman bring me a dream #
- # Bum-bum-bum-bum # - # Ba-bum-ba-bum Ba-bum-ba-bum-ba-bum #
# Ba-bum-ba-bum-ba-bum #
- # Bum-bum-bum-bum # #
Shit !
- Oh ! - Hey . Hey , Miss Wittington . What 's goin ' on ?
- My house was broken into . - No shit ?
No shit .
Hasn 't anyone told ya ? Secondhand smoke kills .
Yeah , but they 're all dead .
Yeah . Yeah , it 's um ...
4946 Cypress Pond .
Okay . Right , thanks .
They said to give ' em 15 minutes and they 'll be by .
- Jimmy , where are you going ? - Check out your house .
- No , wait for the police . Where 's the fun in that , huh ?
- Are you coming ?
Nah , l-l better stay here and protect her .
Oh-ho ! Right , dude .
Good .
All right , let 's not anyone mess with me here !
Jimmy been suspended five times this year already ...
for gettin ' a little crazy with the stick , all right ?
Okay !
Hoo . Shit .
Shit !
God .
All right .
Nothin ' to fear . The coast is clear .
- You sure ? - Yeah .
- I checked all the rooms and all the closets . - Nothing 's missing .
I don 't think so , but they , uh , they did a real number on your office .
- My office ? - Yeah , there 's crap everywhere .
Oh , and , uh , also they messed up your kitchen really bad , too . Ick .
Good night .
So much for the cops .
Perfect .
- We got beer ! Yes !
- We 'll get messed up , man .
I say we egg the house across the street .
- Shut up , dude . - Why not ?
Shit .
[ Man On TV ] Even a stronger nation than now .
[ Man # 2 ] You see ? You see ? Your stupid minds - -
Jimmy !
Oh , my God ! Oh .
Help ! Andy - -
- Looks like a prank . - Andy ! Oh !
Police ! Anybody home ?
Andy ! He 's not dead !
Team 9-10 requests burglary detectives at , uh ,
4946 Cypress Pond Road .
Hey , Bobby !
What do ya got ?
Looks like we hit the Daily Double here .
- What , another B and E ? - Yeah .
So , whose house is this , anyway ?
Marion Wittington . Dr. Sam Loomis 's nurse ?
He was that shrink that died a few years ago .
He lived here . She took care of him .
Oh , I remember him . I saw a thing on 60 Minutes on him .
Spent his life tracking down that Halloween guy ...
who butchered all those kids up in Haddonfield , right ?
- Michael Myers . - Right .
- Hey , you don 't think Michael Myers - - - They never found his body .
Yeah , but that was , like , 20 years ago .
Fuck me .
Loomis was obsessed with Michael Myers .
This is quite a love fest .
- I 'll call up to Haddonfield and warn ' em . - There 's no way , Fitz .
Just a precaution . Tomorrow 's Halloween .
All right , you tell ' em to look for a guy with a cane and Alzheimer 's .
The guy would be younger than I am , okay ?
I was 15 when he killed his sister back in ' 63 .
Yes , Fitzsimmons . Patch me through to Haddonfield , please .
- Yeah . - Michael Myers .
Yeah , right .
I met him 15 years ago .
I was told there was nothing left .
No reason , no conscience .
No understanding . Even the most rudimentary sense of life ...
and death , of good or evil ...
right or wrong .
I met this six-year-old child ...
with this blank , pale , emotionless face , and ...
the blackest eyes .
The devil 's eyes .
I spent eight years trying to reach him ...
and then another seven trying to keep him locked up ...
because I realized that what was living behind that boy 's eyes ...
was purely , and simply ...
evil .
Mom ! Mom ! Mom . Mom .
- Mom ! Mom ! Mom . Mom !
You okay ? You all right ?
Oh . Oh !
- Everything 's okay . It 's okay .
- Do you need somethin ' ? - Oh ! Uh , yeah .
Yeah , please . Thanks .
- Sure . - It 's okay .
Nightmares .
- Making toast . - Mm - -
No . None for me , thanks .
- Caffeine is not a food group .
- We 're out of Percodan .
Got mail . It 's from your dad .
- Birthday card .
- It 's only two months late . I 'm impressed .
Cash is good . I 'm gonna need it when I go to Yosemite .
- You 're not going . - Yes , I am .
No , you 're not .
Yes , I am , and with your full blessing .
Do you want to know why ?
- Why ?
- Because today is the day .
I can feel it . Today is the day ...
that you 're going to realize that I 'm 17 years old ...
and your overprotection and paranoia
is inhibiting my growth process .
Want to go camping ? I 'll take you camping .
I don 't want to go with you .
Sorry .
- Dad would let me go .
- Well , Dad ...
is an abusive , chain-smoking methadone addict .
Who would attract someone like that ?
- Ouch . - And just think , he left you .
Look , John .
I know you get your smart mouth from my side of the family ,
so I 'll give you a break .
- But point check , you 're going too far .
- No , I 'm goin ' to Yosemite .
- No , you 're not .
- Look , Mom , help me out here .
I need a little more open air . I 've earned it .
Look , I know today is the day , but I think that - -
- Oh , really ? What day is that , John ?
- Halloween .
Oh , I hadn 't noticed .
Look , Mom , we 're through with all that .
We really are .
You know what you 're becoming ? You 're becoming an Oedipal enabler , you know that ?
- Thank you . - I 'm serious !
Twenty years from now , you 're still going to be living with her .
Probably running some weird motel out in the middle of nowhere .
- So this means no Yosemite ? - Correct .
- Now , how do I get out of it ? - Why don 't you want to go ?
Oh , it 's so lame . No , no , no . It 's worse .
I-l went there two summers ago with my family .
Loathsome . No , it 's worse . It 'll come to me .
Wretched . You know ? Okay , think-think ...
campfires , s 'mores - -
Repugnant ! That 's it , repugnant .
I would rather have my eyes pierced .
I 'm very sorry . I wish I could help . I 'm sorry .
- But he promised that - - - No . I 'm not going .
You couldn 't pay me to go .
- Hey , what 's wrong ? - Oh - - Uh , my dad .
He flaked on my financial aid again .
- The bursar 's being such a dick . Now I can 't go to Yosemite .
- You 're not going either ?
- No . - I 'm not going .
- How are you going to get out of it ? - Please .
- Hey . Hold on . We ditch Yosemite .
It means we could have
a Halloween party , just the four of us .
Whole place would be empty . We 'd have the run of it .
- We could have a roaming orgy .
- I love the way this man thinks !
Hope that 's not the only thing you love about me .
- Hey , come on . - All right , let 's go .
REST AREA
Okay . You see , I told you we 'd make it .
When I was a little girl , we used to pee in the woods .
- Ohh ! Uh - - - Don 't worry !
Come on .
Mom , that 's the boys ' room .
Then the boys are just gonna have to deal with it .
Hello ?
Okay . Coast is clear .
Okay . Come on .
I 'll be just next door . Mom 's gotta go too .
# # " Mary Had A Little Lamb "
- Oh ! - Mom ?
I know .
- Mom ? - It 's just the door , Casey .
Here 's some tissues - -
Casey ?
Spiders !
- All right . - Ready ?
You know why you 're here .
The buses leave for Yosemite at 4 : 15 , sharp .
And now it 's time for me to do my obligatory plea ...
that you uphold the standards of Hillcrest .
And that means no musical sleeping bags .
- No booze .
- No drugs , no kidding .
Undoubtedly , someone will ruin it for the rest of them ...
so I just want to remind you that the entire teaching faculty has - -
- Hey ! Guess what this is . - What ?
It 's my history report .
Forgot to hand it in .
Guess who 's not going to Yosemite .
I 'm so bummed .
Guess who has a fever of 102 ...
and has to stay in bed all weekend long .
- You two company ?
- So , what 's the plan ?
Romantic dinner , candlelight , soft music .
- Animal sex .
- You need a hormone suppressant .
You 're embarrassing the newlyweds , Charles .
That 's it . Have a good time .
And why aren 't you going camping , Miss Tate ?
Because it sounds like fun .
And you , Mr. Brennan ?
Guidance counselors aren 't usually a big hit in the wilderness .
Besides , somebody has to stay behind and watch over the three or four outcasts .
Oh , good morning , Miss Tate .
- Morning , Norma . - Your mail and messages are on your desk ,
along with the new quarter budget , and oh ,
surprise , surprise , the drains in the
girls ' shower room are clogged again .
- Can I talk to you alone for one second ?
- But , l-l called the plumber , and he assured me that he will be here as soon as he can - -
Thank you , Norma . Thank you very much .
Wait . Wait , wait , wait . Place of employment .
I 'm sorry , l-l just - - I needed a fix .
- We still on for lunch ?
- Uh-huh . 1 : 00 .
You are , without a doubt ,
the most amazing ,
challenging woman I have ever met .
And what 's wrong now ?
Can you just stop with the
Keri analysis just once , please ?
You can do it tomorrow , all you want .
But please , can I just have today off ?
- Whatever you want . - Thank you .
- Lunch . Don 't forget . - 1 : 00 .
Uh - -
" He turned , just in time to see her enter the room ,
with her long , slender legs that climbed high up her skirt ,
Ieading to two tumultuous ,
round , melon breasts . "
Round melon what ?
Now why do you want to label it like food ?
A-And what kind of melon you talkin ' about ? Cantaloupe ? Watermelon ? What ?
Baby , it 's fiction !
People like to read descriptive adjectives .
- It sets the scene .
- It 's stupid is what it is .
It 's sensual and romantic .
Ronny , it 's unrealistic .
This whole writing career is unrealistic .
Hey , we 're married now ,
baby , we gotta get serious .
- This is serious .
- Honey , I been patient , but this writing thing ...
just ain 't takin ' off , and I want
a baby before I get so old ...
- I can 't get my butt back .
- You gotta give me a chance , honey .
I have to express myself creatively .
We payin ' the bills , aren 't we ?
- Uh ! Fuck me ! Shit !
- What ?
Not you , honey . Hold on for a sec .
You scared the shit out of me !
Sorry , Ronny . I gotta ask a favor , man .
- I 'm not lettin ' you out of here . - Aw , come on , man .
- Jus-Just for lunch . Please . - Look , your mom told me ...
the next time I let you loose ,
I was gonna be fired .
- Look , man . I got a date with Molly tonight . - Mm-hmm .
And I want to make it special .
What do you say ?
Look , I promise I 'll be back
for afternoon classes .
Huh ? I just want to get a gift .
Come on , man , have a heart .
No . No . Can 't do it .
Aw , come on , man . Okay , how about this ?
- You accidentally press the gate . - Mm-hmm .
And when you have your back turned ,
we sneak out .
Ronny , don 't you get your ass fired - -
- Don 't you do me wrong , okay ?
- Not a chance , man ! Cool .
- All right . - Get outta here , get outta here .
Comb your hair .
- Just one more book .
Just one more , and I promise I 'll work with your daddy , all right ?
- Oh . Oh . - Oh , Jesus , Will .
- I 'm sorry . I thought you saw me . - No .
You see me now ?
How are you doin ' ?
You wanna talk about it ?
I think I 'm losing John .
I think he 's finally tired of my bullshit .
How about you ?
You tired of my bullshit ?
I 'm a counselor . I 'm attracted to it .
- So counsel me .
- Oh , no . I know better .
I love you just the way you are .
Do you think it 's possible ...
that something so tragic
can happen to somebody ...
that they never recover from it ?
I like to believe that
recovery is always possible .
There 's a little back story
that I haven 't been , um ...
- completely successful with .
- I know .
I 've tried everything . I really have .
I 've tried everything .
Twelve steps , uh ,
self-help , group therapy ,
shrinks , meditation - -
- Everything . - That 's not everything .
Oh , yeah ?
What else is there ?
I 'm a really good listener .
Maybe . Some night , by a ...
warm fire .
I 'll be right back .
Can I get another glass
of Chardonnay , please ?
- Today .
- Yes , ma 'am .
Thank you .
Thanks .
Thank you very much .
God . I can 't believe we 're doin ' this .
- Desperate measures .
- It 's illegal .
It 's harmless , and expected .
Studies have proven that all teenagers , at some point ...
- in their adolescent lives , have shoplifted .
- What studies ?
Hey . We could have avoided this whole thing ...
if you woulda simply scored some of your mom 's booze .
- Look , my mom 's a functioning
- alcoholic . She accounts for - - - John !
- John , what are you doing here ?
- Just gettin ' some off-campus lunch .
You 're not allowed to have little off-campus lunches , John .
- You know that . You too , Charlie .
- Sorry , Miss Tate .
Come on , I 'll drive you back .
You know what ? Charlie , here .
Go get in the car . I 'll be right there .
What the fuck do you think you 're doing ?
Mom , I 'm really uncomfortable with you saying that word .
Well , then don 't put me in the position , John .
Do you know what day it is ?
Of all the days for you to pull this shit - -
What do you think you can do ?
Just wander around town ?
I don 't ask you for very much .
- Just give me one day !
- Mom , I 've given you 17 years !
And I need you to be responsible .
- Do you know what that means ?
- Responsible . Don 't talk to me about responsible , Mom !
- I just need this one thing !
- Mom , I am not responsible for you !
That 's it . That 's enough .
I can 't take it , Mom .
He 's dead .
Michael Myers is dead .
- What do you want me to say ?
- That it 's over ?
That we should try to get on with
some attempt at a happy existence , Mom .
Because all the shit that 's going on
in your head is leakin ' out on me .
And I can 't take it anymore .
You told me yourself you watched him burn .
- I didn 't e-exactly stay to see his ashes , John .
- Mom , 20 years .
Twenty years .
Don 't you think he would have shown up by now ?
What 's he waitin ' for , huh ?
Okay , Mom . I can 't live like this . I 'm sorry .
Wha - - What does that mean , John ?
If you want to stay handcuffed
to your dead brother , that 's fine .
But you 're not draggin ' me along .
Not any more .
Ronny ?
- Mom , let me . - Where the hell is he ?
- Ronny !
Hey , Ronny !
- Where the hell were you ?
- Norma told me to walk the perimeter .
And where were you when these two got out ?
Eyes up , Ronny .
Psycho .
Okay , bye !
- Dennis ! - Don 't send down any more , all right ?
I gotta go to class .
- Dennis ? - Shh ! The best part .
- Do I get points or what ? - Huh ?
You score . Yeah . Yeah .
Hmm . Well , it just occurred to me today ...
that I 've never celebrated Halloween before .
And why is that ?
Oh , we 've got a psychotic serial killer in the family ,
Ioves to butcher people on Halloween , and ...
I just thought it in bad taste to ...
celebrate .
So why now ?
Mm , because there comes a point in your life where you have to concentrate ...
on what 's right about it .
Really ?
And you ...
are a sterling example ...
of what 's right .
And tonight you get my full concentration .
I 'm honored .
Very good point , A.J. So , what could Victor have done ...
to save Elizabeth ?
Anybody at all ?
Come on , people . Did anybody read the book ?
Guys . It 's " Frankenstein . "
- You could have watched the movie !
Molly . Please .
Do you have any thoughts on Victor and Elizabeth ?
Well , uh - - Um ...
Well , I think that Victor should have confronted the monster sooner .
I mea - - He 's completely responsible for Elizabeth 's death .
He was , he was so paralyzed by fear that he never did anything .
It-lt took death for the guy to get a clue .
And why do you think he was finally able to confront his monster ?
I think that Victor had reached a point in his life where he had nothing left to lose .
I mean , the monster saw to that by killing off everybody that he loved .
Victor finally had to face it .
It was about redemption . It was his fate .
Okay , everybody , um , have a good time !
John !
What ?
It 's a permission slip .
Bus leaves in 45 minutes .
- Go pack quick . - Ma , I don 't have to go .
Go , just go ! Have fun .
- You sure ? - Yes . Look , it 's good for you .
It 's good for me .
So , just call me . You know , call . And call .
If you feel like you 've called too many times ,
call once more .
Have a great time .
Thanks , Mom .
- Hi . So what was that all about ? - Hey .
She changed her mind about Yosemite .
- So now you 're goin ' ?
Ah , I wouldn 't say that .
I don 't know . If we were at the midterm - -
No , she 's doing fine .
No - -
Mrs. Cheney , can I call you right back ?
- Uh , oh ! Oh ! - Damn it !
Oh , Miss Tate , I 'm-l 'm so sorry . I-l didn 't mean to make you jump .
- It 's okay . - Well , it 's Halloween . I guess everyone ...
- is entitled to one good scare .
- I 've had my share . - U-Uh , Miss Tate ,
I know it 's not my place .
If I could be maternal for a moment ,
I don 't like to see you like this .
I 've seen you like this before , and ...
we 've all had bad things happen to us .
The trick is to concentrate on today !
What do I know ?
You just take care of yourself , okay ?
Thank you very much . I 'll see you Monday .
Oh ! Mi-Miss Tate , uh , Happy Halloween .
" She took off her clothes , revealing her satiny-soft femininity .
And Lawrence looked at her with lust in his eyes ...
and said , ' l want to invade every part of your being .
I want to tantalize myself with your sweet nectar . ' "
Old Tanya better not fall for that shit .
- I smell that a mile away . - " And Tanya laughed at him .
' You don 't expect me to fall for that shit , ' she said . "
That 's right , make her smart . That 's it .
- Oh , shit , honey , someone 's here . Can I call you back ?
Oh , no , no , no , no , no . I 'll hold on . I wanna know what stupid line ...
- Tanya falls for . - The same one you did . Hold on a second .
- Hello !
Hello !
- Hey , honey . - What 's up ? Where did you go ?
I don 't know . Some car at the gate . I 'm gonna have to call you .
- Hey . - Wait , wait . What 's goin ' on , baby ?
- I don 't know .
Honey - - Where 'd you - - Ronny !
You always fuckin ' doin ' this . You get me goin ' , and then you gotta go . Ro - -
Hello ?
I keep scaring you today .
Wh-What are you doing ?
Nothing . I , um - -
What are you doing ?
I 'm making the rounds . I still have to check on the kids , but ...
I was hoping I would have the honor of spending the evening with you tonight .
I 'd like the company .
- Give me 20 . - Okay .
I 'm okay .
Hello ?
Do you want to die tonight , Cici ?
- Oh , uh , come on ... in .
Sarah , Molly .
Just checking on the Hillcrest remains . You girls okay ?
- Good . Thanks , Mr. Brennan . - And how are you , Mr. Brennan ? Looking cute as ever .
Thank you , Sarah . What are you two up to tonight ?
Well , we thought we 'd hit the town , pick up some guys .
You know , drop some Roofies in their drinks . Have a whole date-rape evening .
- Oh . Sounds good .
- Care to join us ?
I can 't . I 'm , uh , I 'm having my nipples pierced .
- Oh . - But you two have a good time .
- Will do . - If you need anything , contact me or Miss Tate .
- Okay ? - Thanks , Mr. Brennan .
Behave .
- My stash . Come on .
- Come on . - All right . Send it through here .
Come on , man . Let 's go .
Yeah .
Come on .
John .
Come on !
I got you .
Fuck it .
I thought we 'd do this right .
Come on in .
Oh , I love food . I really do .
I hope you don 't mind if I get really big and dumpy .
- It 's my goal in life . - Oh , no .
I , uh , I always found obesity to be very sexy .
God , you are so Renaissance .
Oh , the buffet has arrived !
Ah , for your pleasure tonight ,
we have prepared Wednesday , Thursday and Friday 's Hillcrest dinner selections ,
ignoring Meat Loaf Monday and Turkey Tuesday .
- Thank you very much . I hate that meat loaf . - Where 's the booze ?
- We need a corkscrew for that . - Oh , I 'll go get it .
- Just don 't start anything without me . - Don 't worry .
I 'm not who you think I am .
Okay .
Who are you ?
My name 's not Keri Tate .
Mmm .
What is it ?
Laurie Strode .
- Strode ? - Strode .
Okay .
I changed my name when I went into hiding .
Oh , I like that . That 's like - - Iike the - - Iike the witness protection program .
What , did you like rat out the mob or something ?
My brother killed my sister ...
- when she was 17 . - Wow .
Well , that 's ... " sucky . "
How 'd he do that ?
With a really big , sharp kitchen knife .
That 's terrible . Take off your clothes .
- You said you 'd listen . - Okay .
They locked him up for a long time ,
but he got out and ...
he came after me ,
but I got away .
But he killed a lot of my friends .
- It happened - - - On Halloween .
- You 've heard the story . - Who hasn 't ?
Michael Myers .
It 's like 20 years ago , right ?
1978 .
And the girl that - - What happened to the sister ? She died , right ?
No , she faked her death .
And now she 's the headmistress ...
of a very posh , secluded private school in northern California .
What ?
Hoping and praying every year ...
that her brother won 't find her .
You 're tellin ' me the truth ?
- Now do you want a drink ? - Yeah .
I 'll be right back .
Explains a lot , doesn 't it ?
So you - - you have been living with this for 20 years ?
Something like that .
But honey , you-you don 't - -
You don 't think that after all this time h-he 'd - -
he 'd still be comin ' after you , do you ?
He sat in a sanitarium for 15 years , waiting for me .
And then ...
one rainy night , he decides to go trick-or-treating .
How old were you ?
Seventeen .
What ?
Do you think they made it to Yosemite ? Do you think they 're there ?
- I don 't know . - I just - - I just want to call Johnny . Just - -
What is it ? Keri , what are you doing ?
- My phone 's dead . - Shit .
- What 's goin ' on ? - Somebody didn 't go to Yosemite .
Keri . Uh , what are you doing ?
- I 'm just gonna go find John . - Th - - This is nuts .
- I hope so . - Jesus ! - Christ !
Ronny , the phones are out .
I know , and there 's a strange car parked down at the gate ,
but I can 't seem to find any signs of trespassing .
- Fuck . - Okay , th-there 's no reason to get upset yet .
Let 's just calm down .
Look , I 'm gonna go look for John and the kids .
See if you can get the phones working , and we 'll meet back at the gate , okay ? Come on .
Charlie !
Charlie ?
Where are you , Charlie ? We 're waiting on you .
Charlie .
Inconsiderate , party of one ,
your table 's ready .
Charlie ?
Hi ! Gotcha .
You shit .
I found these , but no corkscrew .
Come on . I 'm hungry ! Where are you going now ?
To see if there 's a corkscrew upstairs .
- I 'll be right back .
- Charlie .
Shit .
Hi .
- Shit .
Lights up , Charlie .
- No sex games till I 've eaten . - Fuck .
- Charlie . - Charlie , what are you - -
Oh , shit ! Oh , my God !
No !
Oh , my - -
Aaah !
Oh !
- Oh !
# They 're laid to rest before # #
- Did you hear that ? - No . What was that ?
# # [ Off ]
I 'm gonna go check on those guys .
They 've been gone for a while .
- What do you think they 're doin ' ? - Hmm .
- Mm-hmm . - Kind of rates a cheap scare , doesn 't it ?
- Let 's go . - All right .
Please .
Oh , please !
- Hello ! - Maybe they just skipped to dessert .
- What the hell 's that ? - Oh , man .
What the fuck ?
This is a sick joke .
- Oh , shit !
Who 's that ?
- Let 's get out of here .
Keep moving . Keep moving !
Oh , God . Oh , God . What the fuck are we gonna do ?
We go to the dorms , and we 're gonna call the cops . Okay ?
- Come on .
Oh , my God ! Oh , no , please !
Aaah !
Come on !
Come on . Come on .
Get up
Oh ! My keys .
- Fuck ! Oh , God . Oh , God . Oh , my God . - Come on . Come on .
I can 't find it ! Oh , God .
- Find the fucking keys ! - I know !
Fuck !
Oh ... shit !
- Molly !
- No ! - Molly !
Somebody open the fucking door !
Oh , my God !
- Somebody open the door !
- What happened ?
- Oh , God , he 's stabbed . - Can you walk ?
- Yeah . - Oh , God .
- Wait . - Who was that ?
My brother .
Get in there . Barricade the door . Lock it .
- Do as I say , now ! - Go .
Go !
All right , what do we do ? What do we do ?
Try to live .
Go . - What ?
- Jump . Go ! - Keri .
- I 'm not leaving you . - I 'm not leaving John .
Keri !
Oh .
Oh , no !
Oh ! Oh , God !
Oh , God . Oh , no .
- Oh .
Oh , God . Oh . I thought - -
- Will !
Oh , fuck !
Open up ! It 's me !
- Open up ! - Oh , my God !
Go . Go !
Run ! Run !
Run !
Go ! Now !
Mom !
- Mom !
Oh , my God !
Miss Tate , come on !
- Go .
- What ? - Go !
I want you to drive down the street to the Becker 's .
It 's a mile down the road . Tell them to call an ambulance and get the police .
- No , we 're not leaving you . - Do as I say , now !
- Mom ? - I 'll be right behind you .
- Mom ! - I 'll be right behind you . Go !
Michael !
Michael ?
Ohh !
- He 's dead . He 's dead . H-He 's dead . - No . No .
- Shh , shh , shh , shh . He 's dead .
He 's dead , gone . Shh , shh . Shh .
I got it ! Hey , baby , I 'm gonna write a romantic thriller !
- What ? - Yeah , a thriller .
- I love you . - I love you too , baby .
Yeah ! I 'm fine . The bullet just grazed me .
Don 't move .
Load him in ! Shut the door !
- Hey , hey ! Wait a minute . - You , move !
Watch out !
Come on .
Come on . Get up .
Michael ?
Michael !
# Hurray for a child #
# That makes it through #
# lf there 's any way because #
# The answer lies in you #
# They 're laid to rest before #
# They 've known just what to do #
# Their souls are lost because #
# They could never find #
# What 's this life for #
# I see your soul It 's kind of gray #
# You see my heart , you look away #
# You see my wrist , I know your pain #
# I know your purpose on your plane #
# Don 't say a last prayer because #
# You could never find #
# What 's this life for #
# But they ain 't here anymore #
# Don 't have to settle the score #
# ' Cause we all live #
# Under the reign #
# I say , you know of the one king #
# One king , one king #
# But they ain 't here anymore #
# Don 't have to settle no goddamn score #
# ' Cause we all live #
# Under the reign #
# I said , you know , of the one king #
# One king , one king #
# But they ain 't here anymore #
# Don 't have to settle no goddamn score #
# ' Cause we all live under the reign #
# Of one king # #